Guide to the Filmer Stuart Cuckow Northrop Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- PERSONAL PAPERS, 1914-1972; Series V; 4.75 linear feet (8 boxes)
  - Oversize
    - Sound recording: convocation "The Atomic Age", Case Institute of Technology, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 994)
    - Sound recording: Indian music, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 995)
- Additional Material, 1962-1992, undated; Accession 1994-M-011; 0.25; (1 box)
  Addition inventory by Carol King 1994 May
  Received from: Norman Riise, 1993 Aug 16
  - Correspondence
    - Northrop, F. S. C. to/from Riise, Norman, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Northrop, F. S. C. to/from Riise, Norman, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Riise, Norman and Engel. Heino re: F. S. C. Northrop, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Riise, Norman and Sadat, Anwar El re: F. S. C. Northrop, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Riise, Norman and Serra, Dr. J. A. re: F. S. C. Northrop, 1972-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Northrop, Marjorie (Mrs. F. S. C.) to Riise, Norman, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Others, 1979, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980, 1983, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - F. S. C. Northrop's obituaries: N. Y. Times, London Times, Yale Memorial Service, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1979, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Printed material, 1962, 1975, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Writings, 1971-1979, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Additional Material, Accession 1994-M-104
  - Annotated books (Box 1)
  - Annotated books (Box 2)
  - Annotated books (Box 3)
  - Annotated books (Box 3A)
  - Annotated books, notebooks, photographs (Box 4)
  - Manuscripts, drafts, notebooks, note cards, correspondence, 1940s-1970s (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts, drafts, notebooks, note cards, correspondence, 1940s-1970s (Box 6)
  - Manuscripts, drafts, notebooks, note cards, correspondence, 1940s-1970s (Box 7)
  - Manuscripts, drafts, notebooks, note cards, correspondence, 1940s-1970s (Box 8)
- Additional Material, Accession 1997-M-151
  - Driscoll, Robert A.
    - "Philosophy for Non Philosophers: A Quest for Understanding Based on F. S. C. Northrop's Philosophy," [includes letter from F. S. C. Northrop to Driscoll], 1981, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Philosophical notes" [class notes on 'Meeting of East & West,' course taught by F. S. C. Northrop], 1946 September-1947 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Lecture by F. S. C. Northrop [untitled audio cassette], 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "A General Perspective on F. S. C. Northrop's Epistemology," [photocopy], 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Additional Material, Accession 1999-M-139
  See Accession 1997-M-151, Box 1, Folder 4